RG 002:025, Select Committee of Inquiry to Recommend Whether Sufficient Grounds Exist for the House of Representatives to Impeach Governor John G. Rowland Pursuant to Article Ninth of the State Constitution
Connecticut State Library
- Series 1. Administrative Files, 1978-2004; bulk 2004
  - Subpoenas
    - TBI Construction Company, 2004 Februaru-April (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Tenergy Water, LLC, 2004 February-April (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Tietz, Albert, 2004 March-April (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Tilcon Construction, Inc., 2004 March 2-3 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Tomasso Brothers Construction Company, Inc.; Tomasso Brothers, Inc.; Tomasso Group; William Tommaso; Michael Tomasso, 2004 February-June (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Transportation, Dept. of, 2004 March 2-3 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - TREA, LLC, 2004 February-Mar (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Treasurer, Office of the State, 2004 April 2-5 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Tunxis Management Company, 2004 February-April (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Tunxis Plantation Country Club, Inc., 2004 February-April (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - UBS Financial Services, Inc., 2004 April 21-22 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Ultimate Travel and Incentives, Inc., 2004 March 22-23 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - University of Connecticut, 2004 April 2-8 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Wachovia Bank, 2004 April 21-22 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Wertheim, Mark, 2004 February-March (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - White Memorial Foundation, Inc., 2004 April 27-28 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Wilde, Wilson, 2004 February-June (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Hearing Exhibits (Box 5)
    - Hearing exhibit index, 2004 June 9 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Exhibits 1-480, unnumbered, 1994-2004; 12 folders (Box 5, Folder 32-43)
      These are duplicates of exhibits in Series 3.
    - April 30, 2004 hearing, Index, Exhibits 1-43, 1978-2004; 4 folders (Box 5, Folder 44-48)
      These are not duplicates of exhibits in Series 3.
      Although they are in a restricted box, these documents have been redacted and are open. Please contact State Archives staff for assistance.
  - Depositions
    - Deposition schedules, 2004 April-May (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Affidavit of David Hemond (clerk), 2004 April 19 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Ciccheti, Michael H., 2004 April 29 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Hanley, Mary Ann, 2004 April 15; 1 folder + 1 videocasette (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - McKenzie, Jo, 2004 May 18 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - O'Leary, David, 2004 May 10 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Ryan, Marc S., 2004 May 13; 2 copies (Box 6, Folder 7-8)
    - Exhibits for Marc S. Ryan deposition, 1997-2004, undated; 14 folders (Box 6, Folder 9-22)
  - Freedom of Information Act (Box 6)
    - Working draft, 2004 April 5 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Requests (Box 6)
      - Haigh-Sundlun, 2004 April (Box 6, Folder 24)
      - Keefe, Hugh, 2004 April (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Complaint and petition for declaratory ruling by the Office of the Governor, 2004 April (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Hearing notices, 2004 April; 4 folders (Box 6, Folder 27-30)
    - Decisions, 2004 April (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Appeals, 2004 May (Box 6, Folder 32-34)
  - News Articles, 2004 January-June; 17 folders (Box 7, Folder 1-17)
  - Personnel (Box 7)
    - Thank-you letters, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Resumes, 2004; 13 folders (Box 7, Folder 19-31)
    - Meeting agendas, 2004 February; 2 folders (Box 7, Folder 32-33)
  - Business Records (Box 7)
    - Administrative supply forms, 2004 February-June (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Billing (Box 7)
      - General, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 35)
      - James Mintz Group, 2004 January-February (Box 7, Folder 36)
      - Manatt, Phelps and Phillips, 2004 January-May; 4 folders (Box 7, Folder 37-40)
- Series 2. Subpoenaed Documents, circa 1995-2004
  RESTRICTED. Please see Alternate Form Available section.
  - Anthony Autorino (AA), 00001-00005 (Box 8)
  - American Express (AEC), 00001-00506 (Box 8)
  - AMR Associates (AMR), 00001-02501 (Box 8)
  - Auditors of Public Accounts (APA), 02502-03849 (Box 9)
  - Brian Baker (BB), 00001-00030 (Box 9)
  - Benson Cohen (BC),00001-00056 (Box 9)
  - Bank One (BO), 00001-00164 (Box 9)
  - Calabrese & Kuncas (C&K), 00001-00117 (Box 9)
  - Cicchetti & Torrance (C&T) (Box 9)
    - 00001-01136 (Box 9)
    - 01137-04195 (Box 10)
    - 04196-05277 (Box 11)
  - Carmedy & Torrance (CA&T), 00001-00258 (Box 11)
  - Connecticut Attorney General (CAG) (Box 11)
    - 00001-01310 (Box 11)
    - 01311-01616 (Box 12)
  - Christine Corey (CC), 00001-00008 (Box 12)
  - Country Club of Waterbury (CCW), 00001-00047 (Box 12)
  - Connecticut Development Authority (CDA) (Box 12)
    - 00001-02499 (Box 12)
    - 02500-05000 (Box 13)
    - 05500-08499 (Box 14)
    - 08500-10863 (Box 15)
  - Corrinne D. Bowie (CDB), 00001-00003 (Box 15)
  - Connecticut Ethics Commission (CEC) (Box 15)
    - 00001-00499 (Box 15)
    - 00500-03211 (Box 16)
  - Connecticut Ethics Commission-S (CEC-S) (Box 16)
    - 03212-03745 (Box 16)
    - 03746-06999 (Box 17)
    - 07000-09999 (Box 18)
    - 10000-12500 (Box 19)
    - 13000-13917 (Box 20)
  - Columbi Funds (CF), 00001-00024 (Box 20)
  - Citigroup (CG), 00001-00075 (Box 20)
  - Connecticut Health and Educational Facilities Authority (CHEFA) (Box 20)
    - 00006-01999 (Box 20)
    - 02000-03847 (Box 21)
  - Connecticut Housing Finance Authority (CHFA), 00001-00067 (Box 21)
  - Christopher Link (CL), 00001-00045 (Box 21)
  - Connecticut Lottery Corporation (CLC) (Box 21)
    - 00001-00999 (Box 21)
    - 01000-03443 (Box 22)
  - CMD Ventures (CMD), 00001-00069 (Box 22)
  - Connecticut Natural Gas (CNG) (Box 22)
    - 00001-00499 (Box 22)
    - 00500-03499 (Box 23)
    - 03500-06499 (Box 24)
    - 06500-09529 (Box 25)
  - Committee of Inquiry (COI), 00042-00531 (Box 26)
  - Comptroller's Office (COMP), 00001-00066 (Box 26)
  - Cocchiola Paving (CPI), 00001-01426 (Box 26)
  - Department of Administrative Services (DAS), 00001-00499 (Box 26)
  - Department of Children and Families (DCF) (Box 27)
    - 00500-03750 (Box 27)
    - 03751-06803 (Box 28)
    - 06805-07278 (Box 29)
  - Department of Environmental Protection (DEP), 00001-00004 (Box 29)
  - Department of Information Technology (DIT) (Box 29)
    - 00001-02912 (Box 29)
    - 02913-06199 (Box 30)
    - 06200-09499 (Box 31)
    - 09500-12799 (Box 32)
    - 12800-15999 (Box 33)
    - 16000-19299 (Box 34)
    - 19300-22499 (Box 35)
    - 22500-25370 (Box 36)
  - Department of Motor Vehicles (DMV), 00001-00081 (Box 36)
  - David O' Leary (DO), 00001 (Box 36)
  - Department of Transportation (DOT) (Box 36)
    - 00001-02999 (Box 37)
    - 03000-06299 (Box 38)
    - 06300-09499 (Box 39)
    - 09500-12499 (Box 40)
    - 12500-15499 (Box 41)
    - 15500-17585 (Box 42)
  - Dolphin Pools & Spas (DPS), 00001-00004 (Box 42)
  - Department of Public Safety (DPSY), 00001-00320 (Box 42)
  - Department of Public Works (DPW) (Box 42)
    - 00001-00899 (Box 42)
    - 00900-03741 (Box 43)
    - 04113-06999 (Box 44)
    - 07000-09499 (Box 45)
    - 09500-12499 (Box 46)
    - 12500-15499 (Box 47)
    - 15500-18499 (Box 48)
    - 18500-20999 (Box 49)
    - 21000-24014 (Box 50)
    - 24015-26999 (Box 51)
    - 27000-28901 (Box 52)
  - Executive Chambers Conservancy (ECC), 00001-00379 (Box 52)
  - Economic and Community Development, Department of (ECD) (Box 52)
    - 00001-00502 (Box 52)
    - 00503-03499 (Box 53)
    - 03500-06499 (Box 54)
    - 06500-09499 (Box 55)
    - 09500-12546 (Box 56)
  - Edward Mikenas (EM), 00001 (Box 56)
  - Fleet Boston Financial (FBFC) (Box 57)
    - 00001-02900 (Box 57)
    - 03000-05999 (Box 58)
    - 06000-06439 (Box 59)
  - First Development Group (FDG), 00001-00659 (Box 59)
  - Fallon Moving & Storage (FMS), 00001-00026 (Box 59)
  - First Union National Bank (FUNB), 00001-00094 (Box 59)
  - Griswold Inn (GI), 00001-00025 (Box 59)
  - Glenn Lauzier (GL), 00001-00016 (Box 59)
  - Governor's Office (GO) (Box 59)
    - 00001-01499 (Box 59)
    - 01500-0399 (Box 60)
    - 04000-06999 (Box 61)
    - 07000-09999 (Box 62)
    - 10000-12999 (Box 63)
    - 13000-15999 (Box 64)
    - 16000-18999 (Box 65)
    - 19000-21999 (Box 66)
    - 22000-24999 (Box 67)
    - 24500-26999 (Box 68)
    - 27000-29502 (Box 69)
    - 29503-31999 (Box 70)
    - 32000-34499 (Box 71)
    - 34500-37499 (Box 72)
    - 37500-40499 (Box 73)
    - 40500-43499 (Box 74)
    - 43500-46499 (Box 75)
    - 46500-49500 (Box 76)
    - 49501-52504 (Box 77)
    - 52505-55499 (Box 78)
    - 55500-58502 (Box 79)
    - 58503-61499 (Box 80)
    - 61500-64499 (Box 81)
    - 64500-67499 (Box 82)
    - 67500-70499 (Box 83)
    - 70500-73499 (Box 84)
    - 73500-76571 (Box 85)
    - 76572-79499 (Box 86)
    - 79500-82516 (Box 87)
    - 82517-85499 (Box 88)
    - 85500-88499 (Box 89)
    - 88500-91499 (Box 90)
    - 91500-94499 (Box 91)
    - 94500-97499 (Box 92)
    - 97500-98286 (Box 93)
  - Governor's Press Office (GOVPRESS), 00001-00049 (Box 93)
  - Governor's Residence Conservancy (GRC) (Box 93)
    - 00001-01999 (Box 93)
    - 02000-02949 (Box 94)
  - Hartford Downtown Revival (HDR), 00001-00706 (Box 94)
  - Hearing Exhibits April 30, 2004 Hearing (HEARING 4/30/04), 00001-00216 (Box 94)
  - HRW Associates (HRW), 00001-00090 (Box 94)
  - John G. Rowland (JGR) (Box 94)
    - 00001-01003 (Box 94)
    - 01004-03140 (Box 95)
  - James K. Robertson (JKR), 00001-00011 (Box 95)
  - Jo McKenzie (JM), 00001-00077 (Box 95)
  - JP Morgan Chase (JPMC), 00001-00069 (Box 95)
  - Key Air (KA), 00001-00033 (Box 95)
  - Keastle Boos (KB), 00001 (Box 95)
  - Kurt Claywell (KC), 00003-00047 (Box 95)
  - Kathleen Lepak (KL), 00001-00002 (Box 95)
  - Kathleen Mengacci (KM), 00001-00012 (Box 95)
  - Kristine Ragaglia (KR), 00001 (Box 95)
  - Lawrence Alibozek (LA), 00001-00005 (Box 96)
  - Madison Beach Club (MBC), 00001-00016 (Box 96)
  - MBNA America (MBNA), 00001-00016 (Box 96)
  - Maurice Fabiani (MF), 00001-00002 (Box 96)
  - Miner's (MINERS), 00001-00006 (Box 96)
  - Marybeth Keene (MBK), 00001 (Box 96)
  - Manatt, Phelps & Phillipps (MPP) (Box 96)
    - 00001-02999 (Box 96)
    - 03000-05999 (Box 97)
    - 06000-08920 (Box 98)
  - Mike Santogatta (MS), 00001-00003 (Box 98)
  - Maria's Travels (MT), 00001-00054 (Box 98)
  - Richard T. Mulready (MULREADY), 00001-00002 (Box 98)
  - Nextel Communications (NC), 00001-00951 (Box 99)
  - Norfleet Press (NP), 00001-00121 (Box 99)
  - O & G Industries (O&GI) (Box 99)
    - 00001-01999 (Box 99)
    - 02000-04999 (Box 100)
    - 05000-07645 (Box 101)
  - Office of Legislation Research (OLR) (Box 101)
    - 00001-00466 (Box 101)
    - 00467-00618 (Box 102)
  - Office of Policy and Management (OPM) (Box 102)
    - 00001-02999 (Box 102)
    - 03000-05999 (Box 103)
    - 06000-08999 (Box 104)
    - 09000-11999 (Box 105)
    - 12000-14999 (Box 106)
    - 15000-17999 (Box 107)
    - 18000-20999 (Box 108)
    - 21000-23999 (Box 109)
    - 24000-26999 (Box 110)
    - 27000-29999 (Box 111)
    - 30000-32999 (Box 112)
    - 33000-35999 (Box 113)
    - 36000-38999 (Box 114)
    - 39000-41999 (Box 115)
    - 42000-44999 (Box 116)
    - 45000-47999 (Box 117)
    - 48000-50999 (Box 118)
    - 51000-53999 (Box 119)
    - 54000-56999 (Box 120)
    - 57000-59999 (Box 121)
    - 60000-62999 (Box 122)
    - 63000-65999 (Box 123)
    - 66000-68999 (Box 124)
    - 69000-71999 (Box 125)
    - 72000-74999 (Box 126)
    - 75000-77999 (Box 127)
    - 78000-80999 (Box 128)
    - 81000-83999 (Box 129)
    - 84000-86999 (Box 130)
    - 87000-89999 (Box 131)
    - 90000-92999 (Box 132)
    - 93000-95999 (Box 133)
    - 96000-98999 (Box 134)
    - 99000-102000 (Box 135)
    - 102000-104999 (Box 136)
    - 105000-107999 (Box 137)
    - 108000-110999 (Box 138)
    - 111000-113999 (Box 139)
    - 114000-116999 (Box 140)
    - 117000-118214 (Box 141)
  - Patrick Baker & Sons (PB&S), 00001-00029 (Box 141)
  - P.J. Delahunty (PJD), 00001-00019 (Box 141)
  - Property Management People (PMP), 00001-00003 (Box 141)
  - Patricia Rowland (PR), 00001-00880 (Box 141)
  - Properties Review Board (PRB) (Box 141)
    - 00001-01077 (Box 141)
    - 01078-03999 (Box 142)
    - 04000-04821 (Box 143)
  - Price Waterhouse Coopers (PWC), 00001-00090 (Box 143)
  - Quick & Reilly (QR), 00001-00090 (Box 143)
  - Richard Gray (RG) (Box 143)
    - 00001-00999 (Box 144)
    - 01000-03986 (Box 144)
  - RMK Prospect Associates (RMK), 00001-00939 (Box 145)
  - Ron Shortell (RS), 00001-00009 (Box 145)
  - Republican State Central Commission (RSCC), 00001-00553 (Box 145)
  - Robert V. Matthews (RVM) (Box 145)
    - 00001-01499 (Box 145)
    - 01500-03156 (Box 146)
  - State Attorneys' Office (SAO), 00001-00090 (Box 146)
  - Secor Cassidy (SCM), 00001-00204 (Box 146)
  - State Elections Enforcement Commission (SEEC), 00001-00106 (Box 146)
  - Richard Sheeler (SHEELER), 00001-00013 (Box 146)
  - Steve Leahy (SL), 00001-00002 (Box 146)
  - Stackpole Moore & Tryon (SMT) 00001-00014 (Box 146)
  - Shared Technologies Fairchild (STF), 00001-00205 (Box 146)
  - Tilcon (TC), 00001-00250 (Box 146)
  - Tomasso Entities (TOM) (Box 146)
    - 00001-00499 (Box 146)
    - 00500-03502 (Box 147)
    - 03503-05069 (Box 148)
  - Town of Prospect (TP) (Box 148)
    - 00001-01508 (Box 148)
    - 01509-02534 (Box 149)
  - Peter V. Tytell (TYT), 00001-00022 (Box 149)
  - UBS Financial Services (UBS), 00001-00084 (Box 149)
  - University of Connecticut (UC), 00001-00040 (Box 149)
  - UST (UST), 00001-00242 (Box 149)
  - Ultimate Travel (UT), 00001-00074 (Box 149)
  - Vincent DeRosa (VD), 00001-00121 (Box 149)
  - Verizon Wireless (VW), 00001-00028 (Box 149)
  - Windsor Avenue, LP (WALP), 00001-00025 (Box 149)
  - Wachovia Bank (WB), 00001-00060 (Box 149)
  - White Memorial Foundation (WMF), 00001-00061 (Box 149)
  - Wayne Pratt (WP), 00001-00190 (Box 149)
  - W.R. Berkley Corporation (WRB), 00001-00025 (Box 149)
  - Wilson Wilde (WW), 00001-00481 (Box 149)
  - Yarmouth Management (YM), 00001-00005 (Box 149)
  - Department of Transportation (Box 150-204)
    Unarranged.
- Series 3. Evidentiary Hearing Exhibits, circa 1989-2004
  - 1-338 (set 1) (Box 205)
  - 339-524, G1-2, J1-3, timelines (set 1) (Box 206)
    There is no Exhibit 357.
  - 1-338 (set 2) (Box 207)
  - 339-524, G1-2, J1-3, timelines (set 2) (Box 208)
- Series 4. Evidentiary Hearing Videotapes, 2004 June 8-21
  Produced by Connecticut Network (CT-N).
  There is no videotape for Hearing Day 2.
  - Hearing Day 1, 2004 June 8; 4 copies (Box 209)
  - Hearing Day 3, 2004 June 10; 2 copies (Box 209)
    Tapes are misdated July 10, 2004.
  - Hearing Day 4, 2004 June 14; 2 copies (Box 209)
    Tapes are misdated July 14, 2004.
  - Hearing Day 5, 2004 June 15; 5 copies (Box 209)
  - Hearing Day 6, 2004 June 16; 5 copies (Box 209)
  - Hearing Day 7, 2004 June 17; 4 copies (Box 209)
  - Hearing Day 7, 2004 June 17; 6 copies (Box 210)
  - Hearing Day 8, 2004 June 18; 9 copies (Box 210)
  - Hearing Day 9, 2004 June 21; 6 copies (Box 210)
  - Capitol News Briefing: Following the State Ethics Commission Meeting, 2004 September 29; 1 video disc (Box 210)